We have to assume that this is the work
of a Conjurer.
[Killua] You're right. No doubt about it.
These buildings weren't here yesterday.
This has to be Nen.
Oh, man, these guys are out
of their minds.
They have someone who can conjure up
entire buildings!
We should be prepared
for any traps they've set.
[Killua] Yeah. It also pretty much proves
they're still around here somewhere.
The problem is these buildings create
way too many blind spots.
I can only see 20 percent
of the area at one time.
[Kurapika]
But if you move around too much,
there's a chance you might
run into one of them.
I'd really like to avoid that.
The thing is, I have no idea what I'd do
if I heard their voices behind me.
My heart is already pounding.
-Voices, huh?
-[Killua] What?
Nothing. Never mind.
Just go back to your post
for the time being.
I'll call you back in five minutes.
Melody. How are things going on your end?
-We're still shopping.
-[Neon] I wanna see that one!
This is harder than normal bodyguard work.
-[Neon] I guess it's not too bad.
-I think Basho's about to snap.
[Neon] Let's go back to the other store!
Okay, I understand.
[crashing]
[theme music playing]
Beloved x And x Beleaguered
[Chrollo] Just to be perfectly clear,
you've already told me
everything Uvo knew about the chain user?
[Shalnark] Yeah.
When we were investigating
the Nostrade family
using the Hunter website,
Uvo pointed out the three at the top
as the members he thought he recognized.
It was late on the night of the first,
when we realized
that they were the daughter's bodyguards.
And the girl... it was just yesterday
when I met her.
That's when you stole her ability,
wasn't it?
-The first time you made contact?
-[Chrollo] Yes.
And here is an updated list
of all the bodyguards in question.
There are two new members.
Oh, wow.
They already updated it?
That was so fast.
So I count seven bodyguards.
There might even be more than that.
That's an awful lot of people
to guard one little girl.
[Phinks] He loves his daughter.
[Chrollo] More like he holds her ability
in higher regard than the girl herself.
Her father got to where he is today
by capitalizing on her power.
And of course, there are many
who resent his advancement.
But why did she come to Yorknew City
in the first place?
My guess, she's here for the auction.
[thunder crashing]
Are you okay?
[Chrollo] Shizuku, Pakunoda.
[Pakunoda] We're listening.
Nice.
How could I have been so blind?
Damn it, what's wrong with me?
Nostrade's daughter comes to Yorknew City.
Why? If only I had thought about it...
perhaps we could have found
the chain user sooner.
It's safe to assume that this girl
came to Yorknew for the auction,
along with her bodyguards.
I was too focused on her fortune-telling
ability to give it much thought.
According to the website,
she's known to collect certain body parts.
It would seem that's her hobby.
Body parts? The Scarlet Eyes!
That's right.
Which means that the chain user joined
the Nostrade family for a reason.
He knew that the Scarlet Eyes
would be sold at the auction
and that Nostrade's daughter
would be interested in buying them.
The chain user wants two things.
To exact revenge on us
and retrieve the eyes.
Okay, Shal, what about the Scarlet Eyes?
Were we able to retrieve them?
Sorry, but I'm not sure.
I had the auctioneer running on autopilot
for pretty much the whole auction.
[Chrollo] Kortopi, do you remember
copying the Scarlet Eyes?
Yes, I did.
[Chrollo] Your copies function as your En.
So can you tell where the copy is?
Yes, if I'm touching the original.
I found them.
[Kortopi] Got it.
There's something of the same shape
in that direction,
approximately 2,500 meters.
[Nobunaga] Is the chain user there?
[Kortopi] We should hurry.
The effects of the En will fade
in a few hours.
Do you have the map?
[Phinks] Here.
[Chrollo] North by northwest...
Twenty-five-hundred meters...
The Beitacle Hotel.
[Nobunaga] Boss...
Let me go check it out.
I beg you.
Very well.
-[gasps]
-[Chrollo] But I'm coming with you.
-You got it.
-Paku, Machi, Shizuku.
You're coming, too.
-Shal, you'll switch with Kortopi.
-Okay.
[phone vibrating]
[Killua] Hello?
-[Melody] Is this Killua?
-[Killua] Yeah, who are you?
[Melody] One of Kurapika's colleagues.
Could you look to your left?
Hang up and whisper a command to me.
Anything at all.
Raise your right hand.
[Killua] That's a hell of an ear!
That's gonna come in handy.
[Nobunaga]
Really? Didn't we already go there before?
I thought the Beitacle Hotel...
Isn't that one of the places
the Nostrade family was staying?
It was, but by the time Shal got to look
at the Hunter website,
they had already checked out
of their rooms.
[Chrollo] They probably checked
back into the same hotel
under a different name.
They're being cautious.
The rain makes it difficult
to make out what they're saying,
but there's a group of people
talking over there.
There are five or six of them,
including some women.
And they're all headed
away from those abandoned buildings.
That's amazing.
Gon and I have done a lot of training
but I can’t hear that.
Because it’s my ability.
For Kurapika to ask me for my help,
I’m guessing he must be getting
really desperate.
Think so?
He wants to do everything by himself,
doesn't he?
Oh, you're right. He sure does.
Would you happen to be an assassin?
Well, I used to be. How did you know?
[Melody] Your footsteps.
You're right beside me,
but they're estinto.
Esti-what?
Estinto. It's a musical term
that means they're just barely audible.
[Killua] Oh. I guess I’m in the habit
of moving silently.
[Melody] Yours are the quietest
I've ever heard.
Your technique is very impressive.
It's easy to see why Kurapika
would rely on you.
Maybe. But I’m not too thrilled
about this.
Oh, is that so?
[gasps] Wait, stop.
They're 100 meters away,
just around the next corner.
You can pick out their footsteps?
Each person’s has their own unique sound.
Oh. I'll check it out.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Killua.
-[Killua] The woman's here.
-She is?
[Killua] She's with her buddies.
There are six of them.
-The guy with the topknot’s here, too.
-[Gon groans]
There's one more thing.
There's a guy we didn't see yesterday.
I'm willing to bet he's the leader.
[Gon] What’s he look like?
[Killua] He's wearing a black coat
with an inverted cross on the back.
He has black, slicked-back hair.
I can't see his face.
Damn it! They're really alert.
I'm too scared to circle around front.
Give it to me. Where are you now?
[Killua] In front of the Motoba Building.
They're heading west on Continental.
[Kurapika] There's a station nearby.
Can you board their train?
[Killua] Depends.
If it's crowded, I can manage.
Hurry. Head to the south.
[munching] Okay!
[Killua] Melody's in the same car as them.
We're headed toward Castor.
I'm in the last car on the train.
Heading to Castor?
The auction site's in that direction.
[Kurapika]
For that matter, so is our hotel.
[Squala]
Yeah. Yeah. I know, Eliza, I know.
Honestly, I'm starting to get
pretty sick of this job!
I should be happy
I'm spending time with the dogs?
Hmm. It sure beats taking care
of that spoiled brat, I guess.
I'm fond of Ms. Neon,
but she's just so... hyper.
Look at this, Eliza!
It's so cute!
[grunts]
[sighs] Well, won't be much longer.
-I'll find a better job, and--
-[growling]
[knocking on door]
-[Squala] Who's there?
-[man] Room service.
[Squala] Leave it by the door.
[Squala whistles]
[dog growling and barking]
Okay, let's eat.
Man, I have really gotta find
another job and fast.
I don't have the energy
for this kind of work.
I just need to find something
that will support Eliza and these guys.
But that's easier said than done.
[dog whining]
Huh?
Don't worry, buddy.
I'll figure something out soon.
[phone vibrating]
[Killua] They got off.
They got off at Liber Station,
and they're heading
for the Saloma Mall exit.
Not good. The hotel is that way.
[dialing]
Seriously? They found out
we switched our rooms?
[groans] This isn't funny!
We need to get out of here now!
I better take these with me.
[Leorio] The station's over there.
Should we get a little closer?
[Kurapika] No.
Any closer than this
then the Troupe might sense my hostility.
Hey, Gon.
This is far as it’s safe to go.
I need to be this far from the station
or else they’ll notice me
before I want them to.
It'll take approximately 0.5 seconds
to land an attack.
And that’s more than enough time
for them to engage an evasive maneuver.
Unless they're distracted, of course.
[both gasp]
The spiders!
It's moving. Descending slowly.
So, on an elevator. Are they leaving?
Let's hurry up and get in there, then.
We will apprehend him as a group.
Try to stay close enough
to provide assistance.
Pakunoda, once we have him,
get the information on Uvo.
Got it.
After that, Nobunaga, they're all yours.
Go.
They're running there now.
And they're fast!
Can we head them off by car?
Well, it is evening rush hour.
At this rate,
-they might be a lot faster on foot.
-[car door opening]
Huh? Kurapika!
I'll contact you soon. Wait till then!
[Gon] Wait, Kurapika!
I have an idea! Kurapika, come on!
Melody and I are still
at the station entrance.
But they just ran off to the northwest.
Right. In pursuit.
[Killua] Wait, you're chasing them?
That's dangerous!
They're gonna notice you! Knock it off!
You there! Damn! He hung up.
What the hell?
[women laughing]
[both gasp]
[woman 1] Whoa, what's that?
[woman 2] Are those ninjas?
[Kortopi] Target is moving rapidly
toward two o'clock.
Then he must be in a car.
I was going to wait
till I found another job.
But not now! Today's my last day!
[Killua] Leorio, where's Gon?
He took off after Kurapika.
He told us to wait here,
but there's no way in hell
I can just sit here doing nothing!
I'm driving to the Beitacle Hotel,
but I'm stuck in traffic!
Grr! Fine, we'll go after 'em!
What is wrong with these people?
Damn it! It's like they just do
whatever the hell they want!
We're being followed.
Since when?
Oops. I was too focused on the target.
Is the chain user behind or in front?
Nobunaga, Pakunoda and Kortopi,
go ahead.
[Pakunoda] Roger that.
[both gasp]
[Chrollo] See them?
[Shizuku] Just shadows, not faces.
One of them's in the alley.
[Machi] The other's behind the trash can.
[Chrollo] Okay. Keep using Gyo.
[both] Roger.
[Kurapika] Come on, spiders.
I'm ready.
[Gon] Kurapika, stop!
We can't fight the three of them and win
if they know we're here! Don't do it!
Guess I'll have to take my chances.
[Kurapika] Gon?
I'm sorry, okay?
I'll stop following you. Just forget it!
[Machi] Him again?
[Chrollo]
The one you mentioned. This is him?
The other one's here as well.
Come on out.
[thunder rumbling]
Well? The Mafia reward has been canceled,
so what do you want with us?
Really, it has? We didn't know!
[thunder crashing]
[Machi] What do we do, boss?
-[Chrollo] Seize them.
-[dialing]
Phinks? It's me.
Come to the Beitacle Hotel.
[Machi] Shouldn't we get rid of them here?
No, I have faith in your instincts.
If they're connected
to the chain user somehow,
we should keep them alive.
My instincts aren't all that trustworthy.
[Gon] Hey, can I ask you something?
How can you kill people
who have nothing to do with you?
[thunder crashing]
[Chrollo] You have a lot of hostility
for someone who's just surrendered.
Perhaps because...
they've nothing to do with us? No.
On second thought, it's not that simple.
My motives are unimportant now.
I don’t like speaking of them.
But surprisingly enough,
or, as I expected...
The reason’s the key
to understanding myself.
[Killua] What's he talking about?
[Chrollo] Head to the hotel
and wait for Phinks and the others.
If they try to escape, kill them.
[Machi] Understood.
[Melody] Now that they're on high alert,
we have to keep our distance,
otherwise, they're bound to notice us.
Make sure you're concealing your presence.
-Damn it!
-We just have to be patient.
-I'm aware of that!
-I don't think you are!
Your reckless pursuit
exposed them to needless danger.
Do you even know why they allowed
themselves be captured?
If you get caught here too, then no one
will be able to stop the Troupe!
[Kurapika breathing deeply]
I'm sorry.
Humans all have to lower their guard
sooner or later.
You're no different. We must wait.
You're right.
[Melody] Where's Squala?
[Kurapika sighs]
He's not answering his cell.
This is not the chain user.
No, but I recognize his face
from the list.
Step outside!
[Squala]
Well, I've got my fair share of skill.
I've survived some close calls.
That experience has given me
a sixth sense.
Right now, it's telling me...
that today, I'm...
[Nobunaga]
Make one move and I'll kill you.
[Squala grunting]
I have questions I want you
to answer truthfully.
One of your associates uses chains,
doesn't he? Where is he?
What are you talking about?
And who are you, anyway?
Do you realize
I'm with the Nostrade family-- [yells]
Just answer the damn question,
or else your left's next.
Hey! Didn't I tell you not to move?
Stay still and answer
the woman's questions, you idiot.
What did you do to Uvogin?
The big guy that you
and your friends captured.
That guy? He escaped from us somehow.
After that, I have no idea!
Where are the other bodyguards?
They already went back to the island.
I was on my way home too, when you guys--
-[Pakunoda grunts]
-[Squala yells]
-There's a penalty for lying.
-But I'm not lying!
Why would I lie in a situation
like this one?
[Pakunoda] I'll ask you one more time.
Where is the chain user hiding?
[Squala] I don't know who you're talking
about. I don't know any chain user, okay?
One last question.
Is there anyone you care for or love?
Do you really think I'd be
in this business if there were?
[Pakunoda] Hmm...
Her name is Eliza.
[Squala gasps]
She's very... beautiful.
[Squala sighs]
If any of you lay a finger--
[thunder rumbling]
I kept telling you not to move.
Just wouldn't listen.
So, did you get any decent data
on the chain user?
It would be far too much trouble
to explain,
so I'll just shoot it into you...
with my Memory Bomb.
I'll stop if you're scared.
Oh, shut up. Go ahead.
[Nobunaga] I see.
So that's what you look like,
Mr. Kurapika!
I'll remember your name and your face
until I get the chance to murder you!
[narrator] The Phantom Troupe has,
at last, identified Uvogin's killer.
Kurapika races to rescue Gon and Killua.
The final battle draws near.
[theme music playing]
-[Gon] Coming up, Gon...
-[Killua] And Killua's...
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I'm Gon!
-I'm Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we'll introduce Nobunaga.
He's an Enhancer and an Iaidō master
who uses a four-meter En radius.
His aura lets him take down foes
with one strike.
One strike?
[both] You're out!
[Gon] Next time:
"Initiative and Law."
[Killua] The keyword is dark adaptation.
-[Gon] What does it mean?
-[Killua] Look it up, dummy.